we're gonna look at the simplest kind of
我们将看看最简单的一种
games that involve time which are called
涉及时间的游戏称为
perfect information extensive form games
完善的信息，广泛的形式游戏
so recall the normal form games model
所以回想一下普通形式的游戏模型
situations in which all of the players
所有玩家的情况
take action simultaneously and that
同时采取行动，
means that it's difficult to use them to
意味着很难用它们来
think about cases where people really
想想人们真正的案例
are doing something in sequence where
在按顺序做某事
there's some kind of explicit time in
有一些明确的时间
the setting here we're going to look at
我们将在这里查看设置
another game representation called the
另一个游戏表示称为
extensive form which makes the temporal
广泛的形式使时间
structure explicit so it allows us to
结构明确，因此我们可以
think more naturally about time there
更自然地思考那里的时间
are two different kinds of extensive
是两种不同的广泛
form games that we'll talk about in this
我们将在此讨论的形式游戏
course perfect information extensive
课程完善的信息广泛
form and imperfect information extensive
形式和不完善的信息广泛
form we'll start with the first case
表格我们将从第一种情况开始
basically they differ by whether the
基本上，它们的区别在于
players are able to reason about
玩家能够推理
everything the other player does or
其他玩家所做的一切，或
whether sometimes they can't observe it
有时他们是否看不到它
so a perfect information game in
所以是一个完美的信息游戏
extensive form is defined in a way
扩展形式以某种方式定义
that's much more complicated than normal
这比平常要复杂得多
form games were we need a lot more
形式游戏，我们还需要更多
pieces to make it work so we need all of
件使其工作，所以我们需要所有
these different pieces here and
这些不同的部分和
intuitively what's going on here is that
从直觉上讲，这是在做什么
we have a set of players as we did
我们像以前一样有一组球员
before we have a set of actions which
在我们采取一系列行动之前
now is just a single set for all of the
现在只是所有
players rather than having a different
玩家而不是与众不同
action set for everybody and then all
为所有人制定行动，然后为所有人
the rest of this stuff is going to be
这些东西的其余部分将是
used to define the utility function and
用于定义效用函数和
in order to get to utilities we need to
为了进入公用事业，我们需要
think about the temporal structure of
考虑一下时间结构
the game so we're gonna build up
游戏，所以我们要建立
effectively a game tree where players
有效的游戏树，玩家
take turns taking actions in the game
轮流在游戏中采取行动
tree and eventually they end up at some
一棵树，最终他们最终到了
node where the game ends and we're gonna
游戏结束的节点，我们要
have a utility marking that note so
有一个实用程序标记该注释，因此
let's formalize that intuition we'll
让我们正式化直觉
start with a set of choice nodes so
从一组选择节点开始，所以
these are going to be the nodes in the
这些将成为
tree where players take an action where
玩家在哪里采取行动的树
something happens and we're going to
发生了一些事情，我们将
call that set of choice nodes H now to
现在将那组选择节点H称为
make the
使
nodes work we need to assign to a choice
节点工作，我们需要分配给一个选择
node all of the different actions that
节点所有的不同动作
can be taken in that choice node so we
可以放在那个选择节点中，所以我们
have a function called the action
有一个叫做动作的功能
function Chi which assigns to each
分配给每个的功能Chi
choice node which actions it is that are
选择节点是什么动作
available to a player in that choice
可供选择的玩家使用
node and we also have a player function
节点，我们还有一个播放器功能
and the player function tells us for
播放器功能告诉我们
every choice node who it is that gets to
每个选择节点是谁
make the choice in that node
在该节点中做出选择
that's the choice nodes we have another
那是选择节点，我们还有另一个
kind of nodes which are the nodes where
节点的种类
the game ends we call these terminal
游戏结束，我们称这些终端
nodes so this is a different set of
节点，所以这是一组不同的
nodes it's disjoint from H and we call
节点与H不相交，我们称
it Z so this gives us all of the
Z，所以这给了我们所有的
different nodes in our game tree now we
现在我们游戏树中的不同节点
need the edges in the game tree and we
需要游戏树的边缘，我们
build those up using the successor
使用后继者建立
function so the way the successor
功能如此，后继者
function works is that it's a mapping
功能起作用是因为它是一个映射
from a choice node and an action that
来自选择节点和一个动作
was taken in that choice node to a new
在该选择节点中被带到一个新的
node and that new node can be either a
节点，该新节点可以是
choice node another choice node or a
选择节点另一个选择节点或一个
terminal node and what we want is that
终端节点，我们想要的是
the successor function combined with the
后继功能与
nodes defines a tree and in order for
节点定义一棵树并为了
that to happen we need to say that
要发生，我们需要说
there's only one way of getting to any
到达任何地方只有一种方法
given new node so the way we say that
给定新节点，我们这样说
formally is that for all pairs of choice
正式地是对于所有选择
nodes and for all pairs of actions that
节点以及所有对动作
could be taken the only way that it can
可以采取的唯一方式
be that the successor function is equal
是后继函数相等
in both of those cases is if the -
在这两种情况下，如果-
whoops if the two choice nodes were the
如果两个选择节点是
same and the two actions were the same
相同，两个动作相同
so these this condition means that the
所以这些情况意味着
choice nodes form a tree which is what
选择节点形成一棵树
we want so now at this point we can
我们希望现在就可以
finally talk about what the players
最后说说玩家
utilities are in the game and so we're
工具在游戏中，所以我们
gonna have a utility function for every
每个人都会有一个实用功能
player and it's going to
播放器，它将
number two every terminal mode so for
每个终端模式第二，所以
each player for each terminal mode we're
每个终端模式下的每个玩家
going to associate a real value which is
将要关联的实际价值是
going to tell us how happy that player
告诉我们那个球员有多高兴
is if they end up in that terminal mode
如果他们最终以该终端模式
let's look at an example this is the
让我们看一个例子，这是
sharing game that talks about a
分享游戏，谈论
situation where a brother and a sister
兄弟姐妹的情况
want to decide between each other how
想互相决定
they're going to share two dollars so
他们要分享两美元，所以
they have two dollar bills and it begins
他们有两个美元的钞票，它开始
with the brother saying how he proposes
哥哥说他如何求婚
to divide the money so he he starts out
分钱，所以他开始
in this first choice node here the
在这个首选节点中，
brother is player 1 and so he has three
兄弟是玩家1，所以他有3
actions that he can take in the first
他可以在第一阶段采取的行动
choice note his first action is labeled
选择注意，他的第一个动作被标记为
2-0 what that means is that he keeps two
2-0这意味着他保持两个
dollars and he gives nothing to his
美元，他什么也没给
sister the second action is labeled 1 1
姐姐的第二个动作被标记为1 1
and that means that he offers to split
这意味着他愿意分裂
the money 50/50 with his sister and the
与他的妹妹和50/50的钱
last action is labeled 0-2 and that
最后一个动作标记为0-2，
means that he proposes to give all of
意味着他建议给所有
the money to his sister in each of these
这些钱给他姐姐的钱
cases after the brother takes his action
兄弟采取行动后的案例
we transition to a new choice node where
我们过渡到新的选择节点
the sister gets to act and she gets to
妹妹开始行动，她开始
take one of two actions in each case she
她在每种情况下都要采取以下两项操作之一
has the same two actions she gets to
具有与她相同的两个动作
accept the offer that he made or she
接受他或她的报价
gets to reject it and the way this works
开始拒绝它以及它的工作方式
is just what you would expect so if she
正是您所期望的，如果她
rejects the offer then both of them get
拒绝报价，然后两个人都得到
a payoff of 0 whereas if she accepts the
收益为0，而如果她接受
offer then both of them get the payoffs
提供，然后他们俩都得到回报
corresponding to what the brother
对应什么兄弟
proposed
提议的